http://bikechicago.com/privacy/

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Please read carefully before using this site. This site is owned and operated by Bike Chicago Inc. DBA Bike and Roll Chicago together with its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively “We”, “Us” or “Our”). By using this site, you signify your agreement to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use this site. We reserve the right, at Our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these terms at any time. Please check periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will signify your acceptance of the revised terms. They were last updated on June 15th, 2010.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy on the Internet is important to Us. As a part of the operation of this site, We gather certain types of information about users. We want you to know the types of information We gather and what we do with it.
Information We Collect
We collect two general types of information from users: personal data (such as names and e-mail addresses); and aggregate data (such as information about traffic patterns on this site; for example, how many users log into this site on a daily basis).
Personal Data
Personal data is collected when users provide information to Us, for example in reserving bike rental/tour, or joining our riders club, electronic newsletters, or other membership services, group inquiries, employment applications, answering surveys, purchasing items from Us, registering for events, or purchasing tickets, and/or registering for contests and other promotional opportunities provided by Us. When you register or request information on this site, We generally need you to provide your name, e-mail address, mailing address, day phone number and credit card information (only when making a reservation), as well as create a username and password. In addition, if you send Us personal correspondence, such as e-mails or letters, We may collect such information into a file specific to you.
Aggregated Information and Usage Information
Aggregate information, such as which page users access and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registration information, is collected through various methods. In the course of using Our site, We also automatically track certain information about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are Using, and your IP address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from Us, Our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to Us.
Use of Cookies
This site also uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow Us to measure activity on the various areas of this site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various parts of this site without re-registering. Cookies are also Us to measure activity on the site and make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Please note: except for personal information provided by you, We do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. You may occasionally get cookies from Our advertisers, which is standard in the internet industry. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to this Privacy Policy.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of a site, such as a member-only area and shopping, contest and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.
Use of Information Collected by Us
We use both the personal and aggregated and usage information We collect for multiple purposes. For example, We collect this information for fulfilling reservations, administering information requests and providing information services, tracking/verifying compliance with Our policies as well as federal, state and local laws, and for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. We may use your e-mail address and, in rare situations, your mailing address or phone number, to contact you regarding customer service issues or billing matters. Personal and aggregated information is also used to: improve the content of the Store; perform system administration activities; customize the content and/or layout of the Store for each individual user; and notify users about updates to the Store or promotional offers or opportunities that We believe will be of interest to you. We will always try to provide you with an opportunity to decline this service when such information is requested from you online. If you later decide you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other information request or distribution, you may also update your account information on the applicable portion of this site or simply reply to any e-mail sent to you and type UNSUBSCRIBE as the subject of your reply or in the message of the e-mail. We may also use your information and activity on the site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce Our Terms of Use.
Disclosure of Collected Information to Third Parties
We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise provide your personal data to third parties without prior permission from you, provided however, that third parties does not include Our subsidiaries, affiliates, licensees, partners, suppliers, industry related services, website hosting partners or other parties who assist Us in operating this site. We may, however, share your data in an aggregate format, as well as aggregate usage information, with third parties for both advertising and promotional purposes. Further, We cooperate with all law enforcement inquires, and with all third parties, to enforce their intellectual property or other legal rights.
Links to Other Sites
It is important to note that this site might contain links to other sites, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Us. For instance, if you clicked on an advertisement banner, this might take you away from this site and to an entirely different site. This includes links to advertisers, bicycle and Segway industry companies, content providers, and business partners, who may use Our name and/or logos as a result of a co-branding or other agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect data and make uses of it that We would not. We do not control these sites or use, or bear any responsibility or liability for them.
Security
The security of all personally identifiable information associated with users of this site is of great concern to Us. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Once We receive your transmission, We use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on Our systems. When credit card information is transmitted, We use SSL (secure socket layer) encryption technology. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while We strive to protect your personal information, We can’t ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Us, and you do so at your own risk.
Terms of Use
Ownership; Restrictions on Use of Materials The entire content included in this site, including but not limited to text, graphics or code, is owned by or licensed to Us. We reserve the right to make changes to the content of this site at any time without notice, including with respect to our products, services, equipment, specifications, models, colors, and materials. You may download, view, and print text and graphics from this site, provided that such content is only used for informational, non-commercial purposes, and is not modified or altered in any way. Except as expressly provided herein, you may not use, download, upload, copy, print, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, post, transmit or distribute any information or content from this site in whole or in part without Our prior written permission. Other trademarks, service marks, slogans, logos and trade names identified on this site are either Our trademarks or trademarks of a third party licensor or other provider. None of these marks, names or logos may be used without the prior written consent of their owner.
Forums
“Forum” means a chat area, bulletin board, photo and video share, or e-mail function offered as part of this site. Harassment in any manner or form on this site, including via e-mail and chat or by obscene or abusive language, is strictly forbidden. You shall not upload to, distribute through, or otherwise publish on or through this site any content that is libelous, defamatory, infringing, obscene, pornographic, threatening, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, abusive, illegal, or otherwise objectionable that would constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party, or otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law. The Forums shall be used only in a noncommercial manner. You shall not, without Our express approval, distribute or otherwise publish any material containing any solicitation of funds, promotion, advertising, or solicitation for goods or services. By uploading materials to any Forum or submitting any materials to Us, you automatically grant us a perpetual, royalty-free, irrevocable, nonexclusive right and license, subject only to express restrictions set forth in Our Privacy Policy, to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, and distribute such materials or incorporate such materials into any form, medium, or technology now known or later developed throughout the world.
We do not and cannot review all communications and materials posted to or created by users accessing Our site and are not in any manner responsible for the content of these communications and materials. We reserve the right, however, to block or remove communications or materials that We determine to be (a) abusive, defamatory, or obscene, (b) fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading, (c) in violation of a copyright, trademark or other intellectual property right of another, or (d) offensive or otherwise unacceptable to Us in Our sole discretion.
Disclaimer
THE CONTENT IN THIS SITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE OPERATION OF THIS SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. WE DO NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
info@bikechicago.com  ·  312.729.1000  ·  © Bike & Roll Chicago
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
